http://www.grip-tek.com/privacy-policy

×
HomeSearchProductsFoam Tubing & Hand GripsGrip CoverGrip TapeGrip WrapAbout UsCompany HistoryPress ReleasesCorporate CalendarPrivaContact UsFind a Sales RepCorporate OfficesBecome an Int'l DistributorDesign GuideGrip-Tek CatalogDesign ConsiderationsChoosing the Right MaterialInstallation InstructionsTechnical Data SheetsFAQs
Call now: 1-888-345-2226
Items: 0
Total: $0.00
View Cart
Checkout
Welcome, Guest! |
Login
| Create Account
HomeSearchProductsFoam Tubing & Hand GripsGrip CoverGrip TapeGrip WrapAbout UsCompany HistoryPress ReleasesCorporate CalendarPrivaContact UsFind a Sales RepCorporate OfficesBecome an Int'l DistributorDesign GuideGrip-Tek CatalogDesign ConsiderationsChoosing the Right MaterialInstallation InstructionsTechnical Data SheetsFAQs
Search Our Products
Go
Advanced Search
Browse Products
Hand Grips and TubingGrip CoverGrip TapeGrip Wrap
Technical Information
Design ConsiderationsChoosing the Right MaterialInstallation InstructionsTechnical Data SheetsFAQs
Grip-Tek Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICYGrip-Tek, a Trim-Lok, Inc. company, does not obtain personally identifying information about its users visiting www.trimlok.com unless the user chooses to provide such information. If a user visits our site to browse our products, the site does collect and store the following information about the user's visit:• the name of the domain from which the user accessed the Internet (for example, aol.com);• the date and time the user accessed our site; and• the pages the user retrieved/downloaded from our site.Trim-Lok, Inc. utilizes the collected information for statistical analysis in order to implement a continuous improvement process.Trim-Lok, Inc. will only send company news and information to those users who have expressly shared their postal or e-mail address for the purpose of receiving information in the future, or who have purchased from or have an existing relationship with us.  COOKIE POLICYTo enhance your experience on our sites, our web pages use "cookies."What is a CookieCookies are small text files that we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your email address or other personal information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, creating an account or requesting a sample. Once you choose to provide a web page with personal information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. A cookie is like an identification card. It is unique to your computer and can only be read by the server that gave it to you.How We Use CookiesWe use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience on our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site). We also may use cookies to offer you products and services.Cookies save you time as they help us to remember who you are. Cookies help us to be more efficient. We can learn about what content is important to you and what is not. We can revise or remove web pages that are not of interest and focus our energies on content you want.How to Accept or Decline CookiesIf you want to control which cookies you accept, you can configure your browser to accept all cookies or to alert you every time a cookie is offered by a website's server. Most browsers automatically accept cookies. You can set your browser option so that you will not receive cookies and you can also delete existing cookies from your browser. You may find that some parts of the site will not function properly if you have refused cookies.Please be aware that if you do not configure your browser you will accept cookies provided by this website.
We have detected that you are browsing the site from . At this time Trimlok cannot accept orders from your country.
To order Trimlok products please contact:
Grip-Tek | A TrimLok, Inc
Company
6855 Hermosa Cir.
Buena Park, California 90622
(888) 345-2226
Facebook
YouTube
Copyright ©2020 Grip-Tek, Inc.
Foam Rubber Tubing and Contoured Grips | Grip-Tek, A Trim-Lok, Inc. company, is a well-recognized and respected leader in the manufacture of EDPM and NPVC sponge rubber tubing and contoured grips.
Grip-Tek provides high quality, superior service and competitively priced tubing and grip products.
Contact UsCareersVisit Trim-Lok, Inc.
